So I closed this one and I come back and I tried to sign into Big Slur.
So as you see, this pop-up has opened over here and it says signing to Big Slur with Google.com.
But I can either choose this pop-up or if you don't have it, you can just click on sign-ups/log-in easily.
And we'll be forwarded to the login page of the very tool.
So as you see, this pop-up shows up and says, "Hi there, welcome to Big Slur.
So happy to see you."
And by clicking on continue with Google, I'll be able to sign in using my Google account.
So again, I wait a little bit.
And yes, it says choose an account to continue to Big Slur suit.
And so I choose this Google account of mine and I wait until the signing-in process is finished.
Yes, so as you see, it says signing to Big Slur suit. Google will allow Big Slur suit to access these info.
I click continue and as you see, we're signed in.
So it says, "Welcome to Big Slur" and it asks us to upgrade, but we don't want to do that for now.